capeads.com 2017-11-01

# Privacy Policy | Junk Mail Blog

**Junk Mail Digital Privacy Statement**

Junk Mail Digital is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you a powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Junk Mail Digital Web (www.junkmail.co.za) site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Junk Mail Digital website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
Junk Mail Digital collects personally identifiable information during the optional registration, responding to adverts and advert placement processes, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Junk Mail Digital also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your postal code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favourites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Junk Mail Digital. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Junk Mail Digital for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Junk Mail Digital website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the Junk Mail Digital public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Junk Mail Digital encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Junk Mail Digital so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Junk Mail Digital is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the [www.junkmail.co.za](http://www.junkmail.co.za/) website and the Junk Mail Digital family of websites.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
Junk Mail Digital collects and uses your personal information to operate the Junk Mail Digital website and deliver the services you have requested. Junk Mail Digital also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Junk Mail Digital and its affiliates. Junk Mail Digital may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Junk Mail Digital does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Junk Mail Digital may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external (third party) business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (email, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Junk Mail Digital may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Junk Mail Digital, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Junk Mail may, from time to time, use any information you have submitted on any of the company sites, including but not limited to Junk Mail, Job Mail, Auto Mart, Truck & Trailer, and AgriMag, to send you marketing material that might be relevant to you.

Junk Mail can, from time to time, also collect and use your information, gathered while you browse the website, for current and future marketing purposes. You can opt-out of marketing communications with us at any time.

Junk Mail Digital does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Junk Mail Digital keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within Junk Mail Digital, in order to determine what Junk Mail Digital services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customised content and advertising within Junk Mail Digital to customers whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Junk Mail Digital will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Junk Mail Digital or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Junk Mail Digital; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Junk Mail Digital, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**  
The Junk Mail Digital website uses “cookies” to help you personalise your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalise Junk Mail Digital pages, or register with the Junk Mail Digital site or services, a cookie helps Junk Mail Digital to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Junk Mail Digital website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Junk Mail Digital features that you customised.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Junk Mail Digital services or other websites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**  
Junk Mail Digital secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Junk Mail Digital secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. Junk Mail Digital does not though store any Credit Card details.

**Third Party Cookies**

Junk Mail Digital use both our own (first party) and partner companies’ (third party) cookies to support the activity on the [www.junkmail.co.za](http://www.junkmail.co.za/) website. First party cookies are owned & created by the website you’re viewing. Third party cookies are owned and created by an independent company, usually a company providing a service to the website owners. Examples of usages for third party cookies are web analysis (e.g. Google Analytic) and search queries.

Junk Mail Digital takes due care when selecting 3rd Party service providers, however Junk Mail Digital cannot take responsibility for the content and use of the cookies deployed by such 3rd parties. You have the ability within your browser to specifically deny 3rd party cookies.

**Changes to this Statement**  
Junk Mail Digital will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Junk Mail Digital encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Junk Mail Digital is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**  
Junk Mail Digital welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Junk Mail Digital has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Junk Mail Digital at [webmaster@junkmail.co.za](mailto:webmaster@junkmail.co.za). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
